JSON IN KNACK
1 After Topic List Save:
field_2979 - [{"id":"1.1","type":"topic","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267330","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.2","type":"topic","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267347","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.3","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#26735e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.4","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#29797b","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.5","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#2f6f8e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.6","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#365ea1","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.7","type":"topic","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#3c45b4","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.8","type":"topic","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#6348c2","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.9","type":"topic","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#945bc8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.10","type":"topic","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#be6ecf","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.11","type":"topic","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d581ca","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.12","type":"topic","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d98cb8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}}]
field_3000 (Color Mapping) - {"Business Studies":"#3cb44b"}

field_3011 - [{"id":"list_1743006033787_t9puq6x","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.4","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.5","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.6","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.7","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position"},{"id":"1.8","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice"},{"id":"1.9","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies"},{"id":"1.10","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully"},{"id":"1.11","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses"},{"id":"1.12","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:33.787Z"}]

field_3030 (meta data field)- [{"topicId":"1.1","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.2","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.3","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.4","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.5","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.6","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.7","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.8","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.9","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.10","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.11","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.12","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}]

field_3086 - []

2 After Generating and and Adding to Bank:
field_2979 - [{"id":"1.1","type":"topic","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267330","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.2","type":"topic","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267347","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.3","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#26735e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":false,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.511Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.4","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#29797b","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.5","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#2f6f8e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.6","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#365ea1","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.7","type":"topic","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#3c45b4","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.8","type":"topic","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#6348c2","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.9","type":"topic","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#945bc8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.10","type":"topic","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#be6ecf","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.11","type":"topic","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d581ca","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.12","type":"topic","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d98cb8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"1.4","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.4"},{"id":"1.5","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.5"},{"id":"1.6","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.6"},{"id":"1.7","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.7"},{"id":"1.8","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.8"},{"id":"1.9","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.9"},{"id":"1.10","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.10"},{"id":"1.11","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.11"},{"id":"1.12","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.12"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"1.4","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.4"},{"id":"1.5","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.5"},{"id":"1.6","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.6"},{"id":"1.7","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.7"},{"id":"1.8","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.8"},{"id":"1.9","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.9"},{"id":"1.10","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.10"},{"id":"1.11","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.11"},{"id":"1.12","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.12"},{"id":"card_1743006180017_0_5ettosp3i","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"What is the impact of a company's pricing decisions on its marketing performance?","answer":"Correct Answer: c) C. Higher prices lead to lower sales volumes but higher profit margins","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"When a company decides to set higher prices for its products or services, it may experience lower sales volumes as some customers may be deterred by the higher prices. However, this strategy can lead to higher profit margins per unit sold, ultimately improving the company's financial performance.","additionalInfo":"When a company decides to set higher prices for its products or services, it may experience lower sales volumes as some customers may be deterred by the higher prices. However, this strategy can lead to higher profit margins per unit sold, ultimately improving the company's financial performance.","cardColor":"#0082c8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:23:05.336Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Pricing decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Lower prices lead to higher sales volumes but lower profit margins","C. Higher prices lead to lower sales volumes but higher profit margins","D. Pricing decisions only affect the company's financial performance"],"savedOptions":["A. Pricing decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Lower prices lead to higher sales volumes but lower profit margins","C. Higher prices lead to lower sales volumes but higher profit margins","D. Pricing decisions only affect the company's financial performance"],"topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"card_1743006180017_1_79fxe8rdv","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"How can a company's promotional decisions impact its marketing performance?","answer":"Correct Answer: c) C. Effective promotion can create brand awareness and increase customer demand","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Promotional decisions play a crucial role in influencing customer perception and behavior. By effectively promoting products or services, a company can create brand awareness, generate customer interest, and ultimately increase demand for its offerings, leading to improved marketing performance.","additionalInfo":"Promotional decisions play a crucial role in influencing customer perception and behavior. By effectively promoting products or services, a company can create brand awareness, generate customer interest, and ultimately increase demand for its offerings, leading to improved marketing performance.","cardColor":"#0082c8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:23:05.336Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Promotional decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Increased promotional activities always lead to higher sales volumes","C. Effective promotion can create brand awareness and increase customer demand","D. Promotional decisions only affect the company's advertising budget"],"savedOptions":["A. Promotional decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Increased promotional activities always lead to higher sales volumes","C. Effective promotion can create brand awareness and increase customer demand","D. Promotional decisions only affect the company's advertising budget"],"topicId":"1.3"}]

field_3011 - [{"id":"list_1743006033787_t9puq6x","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.4","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.5","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.6","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.7","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position"},{"id":"1.8","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice"},{"id":"1.9","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies"},{"id":"1.10","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully"},{"id":"1.11","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses"},{"id":"1.12","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:33.787Z"}]


field_3000 - {"Business Studies":"#3cb44b"}

field_3086 - [{"cardId":"card_1743006180017_0_5ettosp3i","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z"},{"cardId":"card_1743006180017_1_79fxe8rdv","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z"}]

field_3030 (meta data) - [{"id":"list_1743006033787_t9puq6x","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.4","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.5","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.6","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.7","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position"},{"id":"1.8","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice"},{"id":"1.9","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies"},{"id":"1.10","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully"},{"id":"1.11","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses"},{"id":"1.12","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:33.787Z"}]

2 After Clicking Save Button:
field_2979 - [{"id":"1.1","type":"topic","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267330","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.2","type":"topic","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267347","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.3","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#26735e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":false,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.511Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.4","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#29797b","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.5","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#2f6f8e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.6","type":"topic","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#365ea1","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.7","type":"topic","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#3c45b4","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.8","type":"topic","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#6348c2","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.9","type":"topic","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#945bc8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.10","type":"topic","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#be6ecf","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.11","type":"topic","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d581ca","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.12","type":"topic","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d98cb8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z","metadata":{"examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","subject":"Business Studies","lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"1.4","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.4"},{"id":"1.5","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.5"},{"id":"1.6","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.6"},{"id":"1.7","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.7"},{"id":"1.8","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.8"},{"id":"1.9","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.9"},{"id":"1.10","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.10"},{"id":"1.11","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.11"},{"id":"1.12","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:21:46.021Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:21:46.021Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.12"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"1.4","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.4"},{"id":"1.5","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.5"},{"id":"1.6","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.6"},{"id":"1.7","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.7"},{"id":"1.8","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.8"},{"id":"1.9","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.9"},{"id":"1.10","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.10"},{"id":"1.11","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.11"},{"id":"1.12","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:22:46.022Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:22:46.022Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.12"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"1.4","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.4"},{"id":"1.5","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.5"},{"id":"1.6","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.6"},{"id":"1.7","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.7"},{"id":"1.8","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.8"},{"id":"1.9","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.9"},{"id":"1.10","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.10"},{"id":"1.11","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.11"},{"id":"1.12","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:27:29.611Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:27:29.611Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.12"},{"id":"card_1743006180017_0_5ettosp3i","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"What is the impact of a company's pricing decisions on its marketing performance?","answer":"Correct Answer: c) C. Higher prices lead to lower sales volumes but higher profit margins","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"When a company decides to set higher prices for its products or services, it may experience lower sales volumes as some customers may be deterred by the higher prices. However, this strategy can lead to higher profit margins per unit sold, ultimately improving the company's financial performance.","additionalInfo":"When a company decides to set higher prices for its products or services, it may experience lower sales volumes as some customers may be deterred by the higher prices. However, this strategy can lead to higher profit margins per unit sold, ultimately improving the company's financial performance.","cardColor":"#0082c8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:23:05.336Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Pricing decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Lower prices lead to higher sales volumes but lower profit margins","C. Higher prices lead to lower sales volumes but higher profit margins","D. Pricing decisions only affect the company's financial performance"],"savedOptions":["A. Pricing decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Lower prices lead to higher sales volumes but lower profit margins","C. Higher prices lead to lower sales volumes but higher profit margins","D. Pricing decisions only affect the company's financial performance"],"topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"card_1743006180017_1_79fxe8rdv","subject":"Business Studies","topic":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"How can a company's promotional decisions impact its marketing performance?","answer":"Correct Answer: c) C. Effective promotion can create brand awareness and increase customer demand","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Promotional decisions play a crucial role in influencing customer perception and behavior. By effectively promoting products or services, a company can create brand awareness, generate customer interest, and ultimately increase demand for its offerings, leading to improved marketing performance.","additionalInfo":"Promotional decisions play a crucial role in influencing customer perception and behavior. By effectively promoting products or services, a company can create brand awareness, generate customer interest, and ultimately increase demand for its offerings, leading to improved marketing performance.","cardColor":"#0082c8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T16:23:05.336Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.336Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Promotional decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Increased promotional activities always lead to higher sales volumes","C. Effective promotion can create brand awareness and increase customer demand","D. Promotional decisions only affect the company's advertising budget"],"savedOptions":["A. Promotional decisions have no impact on marketing performance","B. Increased promotional activities always lead to higher sales volumes","C. Effective promotion can create brand awareness and increase customer demand","D. Promotional decisions only affect the company's advertising budget"],"topicId":"1.3"}]

field_3011 - [{"id":"list_1743006033787_t9puq6x","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.4","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.5","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.6","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance"},{"id":"1.7","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position"},{"id":"1.8","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice"},{"id":"1.9","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies"},{"id":"1.10","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully"},{"id":"1.11","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses"},{"id":"1.12","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T16:20:33.787Z"}]

field_3000 - {"Business Studies":"#3cb44b"}

field_3030 - [{"topicId":"1.1","name":"What is Business?: Definition and characteristics of businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.2","name":"Managers, Leadership and Decision Making: Role and importance of managers","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.3","name":"Decision Making to Improve Marketing Performance: Marketing decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.4","name":"Decision Making to Improve Operational Performance: Operational decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.5","name":"Decision Making to Improve Financial Performance: Financial decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.6","name":"Decision Making to Improve Human Resource Performance: Human resource decisions and their impact on performance","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.7","name":"Analysing the Strategic Position of a Business: Internal and external influences on strategic position","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.8","name":"Choosing Strategic Direction: Strategic direction options and choice","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.9","name":"Strategic Methods: How to Pursue Strategies: Strategic methods in pursuing strategies","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.10","name":"Managing Strategic Change: Managing strategic change successfully","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.11","name":"Globalisation: Implications of globalisation for businesses","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"},{"topicId":"1.12","name":"Conducting a Marketing Plan: Developing and implementing a marketing plan","subject":"Business Studies","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","updated":"2025-03-26T16:20:37.962Z"}]

field_3086 - [{"cardId":"card_1743006180017_0_5ettosp3i","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z"},{"cardId":"card_1743006180017_1_79fxe8rdv","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T16:23:05.512Z"}]
